# Sam Peterson

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

+11 230 909 8298

peter2020@gmail.com

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

### **EDUCATION**

**University of Kwazulu-Natal** 

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies June 2017 - July 2020

**University of Kwazulu-Natal** 

Bachelor of Computer Science Honours

July 2020 - Present

#### **SKILL**

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

# **ABOUT ME**

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **BACK-END DEVELOPER**

Google Inc

**January 2017 - August 2017** 

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was in sync with everything
- Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

#### **TESTER**

#### Microsoft

July 2019 - Present

- Maintain server
- Provide and facilitate end user assistance
- Maintain computer paraphernalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

## REFERENCE

#### Kutlo Sek, Google Inc

Senior Developer

Email: kutlosek@fakeemail.com

#### **Annah Navaro, CNN**

CNN Correspondent

Email: annah@cnn.com